vacacomparison.com 2015-12-20

# Vacation Comparison is not like apples and oranges, find your perfect get away!

Our goal is to make VacaComparison.com the most trusted site in online travel. To do this, we need your help, so any suggestions for improvement can be sent to us directly via email at [Info@VacaComparison.com](mailto:Info@VacaComparison.com).

VacaComparison.com is a search engine that saves you time and money. We search the web for the best fares and rates; and then you go directly to a travel supplier's website to make your purchase. So, this means we do not take your credit card information and we do not take your hard earned money. Registration on VacaComparison.com is strictly voluntary. You do get some cool information and access to certain great features if you do register, but membership is not necessary to get our great rates and fares.  

**What's Your Sign?**

VacaComparison.com collects personally identifiable information (“PII”) that you provide to us. This includes (at your discretion) your name, email address, password and certain parts of the travel information you submit when you choose to use the VacaComparison.com Trips service (the “Trips Service”). Our software uses the PII to personalize and manage the VacaComparison.com website for you. For example, our site stores your favorite airport and airlines. Also, the Trips Service software uses PII to create and maintain your travel itineraries. If you do decide to give us this information, you are telling us that this information is both true and accurate. Also, you are telling us that you have the authorization to provide us with that information.  
In order to make our site more efficient, we may also collect certain non PII information (such as destination or site usage behavior) based on your use of VacaComparison.com. We may use this information to display advertising that you find interesting and suppress advertising that you might find boring or annoying. For example, we might show you travel offers from your home airport, but not those from airports that are other places in the country. Also, we may use this information to send you target email marketing messages that you might find interesting.  
To help us debug problems with our software (rare as they are), we may collect some technical information from your browser software (such as Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer), screen resolution and the website that referred you to us.

**We'll Keep You In The Loop**

When you choose to register with us, VacaComparison.com logs you in automatically using your email address. This makes it easier for you as you don't have to create and remember a login identifier. The use of your email address for login also allows VacaComparison.com the chance to email you a new password in case you forget or lose your old one. This is perfectly OK and happens to the best of us, particularly those of us that are incredibly busy. If you do register with us, VacaComparison.com will save your information and recognize you regardless of where you login from. So if you are visiting friends and using their computer, we'll know it's you and display your searches and preferences when you do login.  
VacaComparison.com gives you the option of receiving emails from us. We think they are quite amusing, but you may not and can opt out any time. Our emails are sent from a VacaComparison.com address and are sent to your real email address. If you are a registered user and send email booking confirmations to our Trips Service, we will recognize you. If you’ve never registered on VacaComparison.com and you send us email booking confirmations, we’ll send you an email asking you to register. We’ll also send you an email if you send us your email booking confirmations but we are unable to recognize the travel provider or otherwise to create your consolidated itinerary. Every email that we send has an opt-out URL, so you can be unsubscribed when you want. We do hate spam at VacaComparison.com and suspect that you do too.

**In This Case Sharing Is Not Caring**

What's yours is yours. The PII that you chose to share with us is not going anywhere off of our site. We won't sell your PII to anyone. There might be an exception in the event VacaComparison.com itself is sold. In this case we would transfer your PII to our buyers so that they could continue to provide the same great VacaComparison.com service. Also, if you use the Trips Service, you can send, or grant access to, your itinerary to your friends and family. Once displayed on publicly-viewable web pages, that information can be collected and used by others.  
From time to time, we will also share aggregated usage information with others. This type of information does not contain your identity or anything personally identifiable to you.

**If The Police Come Knocking At Our Door**

VacaComparison.com may disclose to authorized law enforcement personnel the personal data from anyone who poses a threat to our interests. This might include those that are attempting to commit fraud or those who conduct activities that could bring harm to others. We assume that this is not you so please don't worry.

**You Are The Boss**

VacaComparison.com members and site visitors have control over the use of their personal data. Since you are the boss on VacaComparison.com, you always can change your account settings in the "My Profile" page on VacaComparison.com. How does it feel to be such a big shot?

**Protecting Your Information**

VacaComparison.com has a sophisticated security program intended to keep the information stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access. We store your information in secure data centers located in the United States. Our systems are configured with data encryption, or scrambling technologies and firewalls constructed to the highest industry standards. We also use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that protects the data you send over the Internet. Third party security firms review our internal security policies and documentation regularly. The bottom line is, when it comes to information security, we mean business.

**Cookies (Not The Kind You Eat With Milk)**

When you visit VacaComparison.com we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more 'cookies'. Your browser will store these cookies on you computer in a small text file. For example, when you decide to login as a VacaComparison.com member, we store encrypted information in your browser so you don't have to login on every page.  
Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. You can enable your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may disable access to some services and tools that we offer.  
VacaComparison.com does make money by selling advertising as well as referrals from searches on our site. Our third party advertising partners often use a cookie or third party web beacon (a single pixel GIF image) to track when a click becomes a sale (cha ching). No PII is ever sent to these advertising partners.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Can We Email You Sometime?**

With the exception of emails confirming registration, emails that include information about your account, emails relating directly to an itinerary or travel profiles created through the Trips Service, and service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your account membership, we will not send you any emails unless you opt-in to receive communications from us. If you opt-in to receive communications from us, you will receive information we believe will be of use and interest to you, including target email marketing messages. If you decide that you are no longer interested in receiving email communications from us, you may follow the instructions in our emails to unsubscribe from our email list.

**Every Website Has Its Own Voice and Policies**

Although we work with responsible third parties, their business policies may include different privacy policies and practices than we have. So when you click through to third party websites, our privacy policies no longer apply. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these partner websites.

**Big Kids Only Please**

VacaComparison.com does not knowingly collect PII information from people under the age of 18. If we become aware of the fact that a minor is attempting to submit this information, we will inform the minor that he or she is ineligible to do so. We will then remove this information from our records.

**Should We Evolve, Change, Self Actualize**

VacaComparison.com reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If there are material changes to this statement on how VacaComparison.com will use your PII, we will prominently post these changes prior to implementing them. If you use our website after we post these changes, this indicates your acceptance of them. Regardless of later updates, we will follow the privacy practices described in this privacy statement at the time you provided us with your information. If you have questions about our privacy policies, please email us at [Info@VacaComparison.com](mailto:Info@VacaComparison.com).

Last updated: November 1, 2012
